In order to string jewelry, you're going to need something to put it on.
I actually started out with fishing line, and you can make knots in it.
But I don't have that today.
I use nylon-coated steel wire, or tiger tail, is what they call it.
And there are different diameters.
There's really thick and really thin, depending on how heavy your necklace is or how heavy your beads are.
And here are some samples.
This is all done with tiger tail.
And that's basically what I use to make basic necklaces.
And there's also stretchy cord, which everybody knows about power bracelets, and that's what they're put on.
And you can just stretch it over your arm, like that.
You do a full knot with both strands or a square knot with that.
And I also use memory wire.
Memory wire goes back to its original form.
Here is a necklace and a bracelet.
You don't have to have a clasp with it.
It just goes back, like that.